Jack Elliott

21 Roscoe Street Stockport SK3 9EN

Jack elliott513@hotmail.co.uk 07799823543

Career Statement

I have always liked puzzles and creative projects where I can make something interesting; after working in various fields such as insurance and teaching English abroad I want to apply myself to a new challenge – which for me is to work in Software Development.

To showcase my commitment to this I used my spare time after work to set up a website on Github, using both Codecademy and the Head First Learn to Code series of books to teach myself, I produced a series of fun projects that tested my grasp of coding. You can see my portfolio here: https://jackofthenorth.github.io/

Initially I would like to work as a Front or Back End developer with the long-term career goal of eventually becoming a Full Stack developer.

Skills

- Comfortable with public speaking and communicating with a wide range of people.
- Able to work alone or in a group, under pressure to meet goals and deadlines.
- Administration, leadership and team development skills from various work environments.
- Excellent interpersonal skills, telephone manner and a team player.

Education

Sept 2018-April 2019 Completed Codecademy training in HTML, CSS and Javascript

April 2013-October 2013 I-to-I TEFL Qualification

140Hr Online TEFL course including 20Hr Classroom based course teaching English abroad

September 2005-July 2008 Bournemouth University Media School

Graduated with a 2:1 in Scriptwriting for Film and Television

I also have three A Levels A-C and nine GCSE's A-C.

Employment History

September 2017-Present Esure Recoveries Specialist

I currently work in the claims department being responsible for recovering outlay in insurance claim cases. I've delivered sales and customer service training to fifty employees, led team huddles, helped develop new recruit training and received multiple commendations from my clients for excellent service.

March 2016-June 2017 Black & White Academy English Teacher

I worked at a private language academy in Spain, teaching a wide age range from five year olds to advanced adult students studying for work purposes. Alongside my teaching duties I created a bespoke Business English syllabus that met Cambridge guidelines, I ran workshops for peer development and took part in observations with feedback of my colleague's classes.

May 2014-December 2015 Shane English School English Teacher

I worked at a large language academy in China. I trained new teachers, gave observational feedback, led staff workshops, delivered presentations and organized school trips and events/promotional work in the community.

Prior to this I have worked at an English school in Thailand; at Barclay's Bank; Wetherspoons; the White Company, Right Home Residential Lettings Agency and Tesco supermarket.

Voluntary Work

I helped organise the 2007 Cheltenham Literature Festival. I have also volunteered in various offices in London and Bath including the Pathé Film Company; Future Publishing; the Blake Friedmann Literary, TV & Film Agency and The Community Channel Television Network.